Diego Araujo

DEVELOPER / IT SUPPORT TECHNICIAN

PROFILE

I'm Diego Araujo, 25 years old, with six years of experience in technical support. My enthusiasm for computer support has been a lifelong passion. My experience in customer sales has enriched my ability to understand and meet customer needs effectively. Additionally, my educational background has facilitated my ease in handling both hardware and software issues.

CONTACT

Phone: 407-953-5229

Email: diegoaraujolive@hotmail.com

Address: 6185 Raleigh St;

Orlando, FL 32835

EDUCATION

UCF Full-Stack Web Development Boot Camp - Orlando, FL (In progress)

HTML, CSS and Git, JavaScript; Web APIs; Third-Party APIs; Server-Side APIs; Node.js; Object-Oriented Programming; Express.js; SQL; Object-Relational Mapping (ORM); Model-View-Controller (MVC); Computer Science for JavaScript; NoSQL; Progressive Web Applications (PWA); React; MERN; State;

Social Opportunity Institute (TOTVS-BR)

June 2016 - December 2017
Practical Theory of Administrative
Processes: features involving
Microsiga Protheus ERP systems
(Purchasing, Inventory, Billing,
Financial) Windows 7, computer
support (hardware and software),
Office 2013

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Hardware
Software
Software Dev
Sales
Customer Service

WORK EXPERIENCE

United Data Technologies (Orlando)

November 2022 - Current

IT Repair Technician: Skilled IT Technician with a proven history of accurately troubleshooting and repairing Dell, HP, and Lenovo devices for prominent school districts throughout Florida.

Contax Participações S.A (Brazil)

February 2018 - January 2019

Telemarketing Operator: performing customer service by phone, registering requests through tools, active or receptive support according to the sector currently operated

W MARCAS E GESTAO DUAS RODAS (Brazil)

January 2016 - December 2017

IT SUPPORT TECHNICIAN: Performing selection, implementation and maintenance of basic and support hardware and software, defining access control to resources, monitoring the performance of installed technical resources, providing support and clarifying doubts to internal and external for company applications via phone, skype and in person

LANGUAGES

Portuguese: Native Spanish: Professional English: Professional

INTERESTS

Travel Reading Gaming Music